(Leonard:)Um, I don't really know
how to say this.
(Colonel Williams:)Well, you could try
starting with "sir".
(Leonard:)Right. Sorry, sir.
(Sheldon:)He said start with it,
not end with it.
(Colonel Williams:)- Sir...
- Hmm?
(Howard:)We've hit a bit
of a snag.
(Howard:)We're already behind schedule.
(Sheldon:)The computations required
to overcome
(Sheldon:)the deployability issues
(Sheldon:)are more significant
than we thought.
(Leonard:)I understand that
we're under contract,
(Leonard:)and I don't know what
the consequences
(Leonard:)of violating that are,
but, uh...
(Leonard:)we're not gonna
be able to deliver
(Leonard:)in the time we promised.
(Colonel Williams:)How long do you need?
We-We're thinking...
two years.
(The Flash:)All right.
(Howard:)That's it?
(Howard:)You're okay with that?
(Bernadette:)You think you're
the first government contractor
(Colonel Williams:)who isn't gonna deliver
on time?
(Colonel Williams:)We're still waiting
for a big space laser
(Colonel Williams:)Reagan ordered
to beat the commies.
(Leonard:)Thanks for understanding,
sir.
(Howard:)Yes, thank you
so much.
We-We really
appreciate it.
(The Flash:)All right,
pressure's off
(Howard(off):)Wanna see a movie?
(Sheldon(off):)Popcorn's on me.